I
with me forever
forever holy
when the union's inspiration
through the workers blood shall
run there can be no power
greater and beneath the sun yet
what force on earth is weaker
than the feeble strength of one
but the union makes us strong
it's all about
forever for the union it is we
who plow the prairies built the
cities where they trade dug the
minds and built the workshops
endless miles of railroad laid
now we stand out cast and
starving amid the wonders we
have made but the union makes
us strong
solidarity forever
they have taken on told
millions that they never toil
to earn but without our brain
and muscle not a single wheel
can turn we can break their
body power gain our freedom
when we learn that the union
makes us strong
forever.
Forever solidarity forever
ever.
In our hands is placed a power
greater than their hearted gold
greater than the might of Adams
magnified 1000 fold we can
bring to birth a new world from
the ashes of the old for the
union makes us strong